

CONTACT

+34 627 849 839

patobottos@gmail.com

Barcelona - SPAIN







• ReactJS

Typescript

JavaScript

Tailwind

• Firebase

Bootstrap

• HTML5

Figma

• CSS3

Wordpress

• Git

• iOS / Linux



SOFT SKILLS

Orientation to results
Proactivity
Autonomy
Teamwork
Analytical capacity
Organization and planning
Customer oriented



Catalan C1

Spanish Mother tongue

English C2
French B2

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Frontend React Developer with over 10 years of experience as web content manager in diverse web projects, including personal blogs, entrepreneurs' websites, and non-profit platforms using WordPress. Proficient in JavaScript frameworks, HTML/CSS, and Git, I like solving challenges and have a keen eye for creative design. Eager to contribute to an organization focused on using technology for the enhancement of people's daily lives, prioritizing the welfare of its employees, and with environmental responsibility.



WORKING EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

IT Academy | 2023

• Nim game app development, following the Mariendbad board version. Using: React, ReactRouter, CSS3, Firebase.

COMMUNICATIONS TECHNICIAN

CRAC Association | 2018 - Present

- Web management with Wordpress. Newsletter design with Mailchimp. Weekly sendings to more than 250 users.
- **Key achievements**: Entity migration to Google Workspace cloud.

WORDPRESS WEB DEVELOPER

pbaudiovisual | 2013 - 2018

- Design and develop custom WordPress platforms for clients, resulting in responsive, user-friendly websites.
- **Key achivements:** more than 10 sites designed.

FORADCAMP FESTIVAL CODIRECTOR

Ajuntament de Figaró-Montmany | 2013 - 2018

- Festival codirection. Web designer with Wordpress.
- Commission editor, programmer and producer.
- **Key achievements:** More than 2000 audience members in an independent documentary festival.

PUBLIC MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT

LTC Project | 2007 - 2010

- Process redesign, development of public service portfolios.
- Organizational studies, creation of public service offices.
- Key achievements: creation of Cunit Citizen Service Office.



EDUCATION

REACT FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER CODING BOOTCAMP

IT Academy | 2022 - 2023

MASTER'S DEGREE IN CREATIVE DOCUMENTARY

Universitat Pompeu Fabra - IDEC | 2010 - 2011

MASTER'S DEGREE IN PUBLIC MANAGEMENT

Universitat Pompeu Fabra - IDEC | 2003 - 2005

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN INTERNATIONAL RELATIONSHIPS

San Andrés University (Buenos Aires) | 1996-2000

Magna Cum Laude diplome